<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Justice Oklahoma on Open Justice Oklahoma Data Blog</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Justice Oklahoma on Open Justice Oklahoma Data Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stat Spotlight: Eviction Filings Are Soaring in Oklahoma County</title>
      <link>/post/2022-06-16-stat-spotlight-evictions-are-soaring-in-oklahoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2022-06-16-stat-spotlight-evictions-are-soaring-in-oklahoma/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Figure 1: Eviction filings are on the rise. Eviction filings across the state have been rising steadily since the onset of the COVID-19 Pandemic, despite eviction moratoriums and assistance programs aimed at preventing people from losing their homes due to the crisis. In Oklahoma County in particular, though, it seems that the dam may have finally broken – in February of 2022, Oklahoma County landlords filed 2,188 eviction cases, which is more than any month on record.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Deep Dive: Oklahoma County Detention Center</title>
      <link>/post/2022-06-14-data-deep-dive-oklahoma-county-detention-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2022-06-14-data-deep-dive-oklahoma-county-detention-center/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          1. The Oklahoma County Detention Center Located in Oklahoma City, the Oklahoma County Detention Center (OCDC) is the biggest jail in the state, currently incarcerating an average of around 1,500-1,600 people. It used to be much bigger – in 2016, the jail’s population peaked at over 2,500 people, X% the jail’s original intended capacity – but reform efforts undertaken in the last few years have successfully begun to reverse this upward trend.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stat Spotlight: Homelessness in Local Jails</title>
      <link>/post/2022-06-13-test-post-ocdc-housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2022-06-13-test-post-ocdc-housing/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/post/2022-06-13-test-post-ocdc-housing//www/jail.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          Data from the Oklahoma County Detention Center sheds light on the issue of homelessness among incarcerated people in Oklahoma.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fancy R Markdown Post</title>
      <link>/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Plain Old Markdown Post</title>
      <link>/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/bean.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          Posts can be plain Markdown as well.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Open Justice Oklahoma</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Our Mission # My name is Radek and I&amp;rsquo;m the author of this theme. I made it to help you present your ideas easier.
We all know how hard is to start something on the web, especially these days. You need to prepare a bunch of stuff, configure them and when that’s done — create the content.
This theme is pretty basic and covers all of the essentials. All you have to do is start typing!
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OJO Research Team</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Ryan Gentzler &amp;ndash; Research Director # Ryan Gentzler is the Director of Open Justice Oklahoma. For over two years, Ryan served as a Policy Analyst focused on criminal justice at Oklahoma Policy Institute, where he was responsible for research on topics including sentencing, incarceration, court fines and fees, and pretrial detention. Open Justice Oklahoma grew out of Ryan&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking analysis of court records, which was used to inform critical policy debates.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>